

Work History

INITIATED STARTUP

Web Developing + Digital Marketing | JAN 2021 - present Have initiated a small start up in team where we serve quality services like web developing and digital marketing to the firm.

FREELANCER

Web Projects | OCT 2020 - present

I have received 20+ web projects till date which were on different technologies from basic HTML, CSS, JS to ejs + mongo db and have given satisfactory result to the project managers

TECHNICAL AMBASSADAR

Non-Profit Organization | 2017 - present

I am contributing in a Non-Profit Organization as a Technical Ambassadar.

Projects

ALEX

Alex is virtual assistant created using JS APIs which has fabulous features from searching Youtube Video, Weather Forecast, News, Quotes, Jokes, e-Books, Stocks etc. to Getting Direction and Playing Games (2048, Hangman, Stone Paper Scissor, Tic Tac Toe)

OPEN-SOURCE

- Particpated in Hacktober Fest
- Twindle
- Dotphy

Education History

CHAROTAR UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY (CHARUSAT)

CSE | 2021 - present

- SEM 1: 9.22 SGPA
- SEM 2: PRESENT

GREEN VALLEY HIGH SCHOOL

HSC | 2020

- 87%

BHARATIYA VIDYA BHAVANS V M PUBLIC SCHOOL

SSC | 2018

- 93.4%

Personal Profile

I really enjoy programming and always love to learn something new. I spend much of my free time working on programming projects and I'm a technical ambassador at a non profit organization and also have experience as a frontend web developer for the same. I am interested in gaining experience in developer roles of any kind.

Contact Details

devarshidoshi007@gmail.com

+919409265208

Manjalpur, Vadodara, India

@DoshiDevarshi

devarshidoshi devarshidoshi

in devarshi-doshi-45571a13b

https://devarshidoshi.github.io/

Notable Skills

- HTML, CSS, JS
- JAVA, PHP, MYSQL

Achievements

- Secured Runners Up Position in WEBCRAFT 2021 CSI DEPSTAR For Web Designing (view here)
- Secured 1st Position in CDC 2018 CSI Vadodara Chapter For Web Designing {view here}
- -Secured 2nd Position in CDC 2017 CSI Vadodara Chapter For Web Designing {view here}
- Secured 2nd Position in CDC 2016 CSI Vadodara Chapter For Web Designing {view here}

Language